now that we've made the bases match we
can drop the base Drop the
Base and we can set the exponents equal
to each other and solve for x since the
Bas is matched the only way these two
sides can be equal to each other is if
the exponents are equal to each other so
in other words we can just drop the
base and that gives us 2x is equal to
138 the only way these two sides of the
equation are going to be equal is if the
exponents are equal so we can just drop
the base Drop the
Base
now since both these have the same base
of two the only way they're going to be
equal is if these exponents are equal or
in other words we can drop the
[Music]
base so we end up with 4x + 1 = 9x - 3